mubawab.com.qa 2012-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Mubawab

This Privacy Policy (this "Privacy Policy") describes the policies governing the collection, use and disclosure of information that Mubawab SL, collects and receives from you. This privacy policy applies to your use of Mubawab's websites and mobile applications (collectively, the "Site"), but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to this one, or any relationships you may have with the business listed on the Site.

BY USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, YOU SHOULD NOT USE THE SITE.

Website owner:   
Mubawab S.L. (Mubawab)   
Calle Provença 277, 7-2   
08037 Barcelona, Spain   
info[att]mubawab . com   
NIF/VAT: ES B-65259699

Mubawab complies fully with current legislation concerning personal data protection and the confidentiality commitments of its activity. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies, except to the provider of your selected product or service.

#### 1- Object

The user data recorded through the forms enabled there for at this website, (hereinafter the Website) are collected by Mubawab, S.L. (hereinafter, Mubawab) with the object of facilitating the provision of the services that Mubawab provides through the said Website; of facilitating the opinion of the users; administrative purposes and push services and other services that might be of interest for the users of the Website.

You may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you: (a) register for the site, (b) register for free newsletters, (c) register for free email services, (d) make an inquiry about a product or service announced in Mubawab; (e) send email messages, submit forms or send other information to us; and/or (f) subscribe to receive services. The user guarantees that the personal data given to Mubawab are true, and accepts responsibility for reporting any change thereto.

The data collected are adequate, pertinent and not excessive in relation to the ambit, the determined, explicit, legitimate ends and services of Mubawab.

#### 2- User consent

The sending of personal data through the use of the electronic forms of Mubawab or, as the case may be, electronic mail messages, supposes the express consent of the sender to the automated treatment of the data included in the indicated media, services and products related to the objects of the Mubawab website, and the electronic sending of communications with information related to Mubawab and its initiatives. Mubawab will send partner inquiries to the partner in question as well as possibly three additional partners of similar value, location and service.

#### 3- Compulsory or optional nature of the information provided by the User and reliability of the information

The User guarantees that the personal information provided is true and agrees to inform Mubawab of any changes to the same.

The User guarantees that the personal information provided is exact and up to date and reflects the User’s current status. The User is responsible for keeping his or her information up to date at all times. The User is responsible for any mistake or error in the data provided, and shall be liable for any damage deriving from said errors, as regards Mubawab or third parties, by virtue of using Mubawab’s services.

#### 4- How the information is used and disclosed to third parties.

As a general practice, we do not provide your personally identifiable information to third parties. The major exception to this practice is that if you provide information to us in connection with a product or service, we may share your information with the owner/manager of the product owner or the service company. We do not sell your email address or your name and personal demographic information to mass marketers, however, on particular pages where we ask for your personally identifiable information, we may explicitly tell you that the data we are collecting on that page will be shared with third parties, in which case those disclosures shall override anything to the contrary in this policy.

In some cases, we use your personally identifiable information to provide information to you, such as to send to you requested newsletters or to provide to you requested services.

In some situations, we share your personally identifiable information with third parties who provide services to our site in order to enhance the functionality available to you on our website, and to provide you with new products and services. We use third party vendors to conduct and/or facilitate a survey of our clients and customers to obtain information on our services.

We use your information on an aggregated basis to do such things as operate our site, enhance our site, and sell and deliver advertising. We also use this data, both aggregated and personally identifiable; to enhance your on-site experience by displaying content and marketing messages that we believe will be of interest to you.

We may use your information to notify you about information related to your inquiry. We may also use your information to contact you about updates to our site and services, and to inventory available from our products owners and services companies.

#### 5- Electronic communications

Mubawab will offer the users the sending of a bulletin that includes all the most relevant news, developments and information on the Website. Likewise, users may give up the bulletin service or modify their subscription data thereto.

#### 6- Security

Mubawab maintains the personal data protection security levels, concerning the security measures of automated files that contain personal data, and has established all technical means in its reach to avoid the loss, bad use, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of the data the users provide through the Website, without prejudice of informing them that Internet security measures are not unbreakable.

Mubawab agrees to comply with its duty to secrecy and confidentiality with respect to the personal data contained in the automated file in accordance with applicable legislation.

By completing and submitting an electronic form to $url_country users expressly consent to receiving bulletins concerning the most relevant news, innovations, and information regarding the website, as well as electronic communications relating to the sector and the following sectors:

• IT and Technology: 

o IT, software and technology 

o Internet 

o Digital TV / Satellite / Cable 

o Fixed telephony 

o Mobile telephony 

• Gastronomy / Food 

• Art / Crafts, Decorating and Interiors 

• News and communications about working with and joining non government organisations / Charity 

• Construction / DIY 

• Pets 

• Business exchange services 

• Purchase and sale of companies 

• Franchises 

• Financial services: 

o Finance 

o Private bank 

o Stock market and investments 

o Brokers 

o Credit: Loans and mortgages 

o Accounts and credit cards 

o Investment funds 

o Mortgages 

o Renting / leasing 

o Insurance 

• Property offers 

• Motor / Cars/ Sailing 

• Leisure and Entertainment: 

o Digital channels 

o Leisure 

o Cinema and Shows 

o Culture / Museums 

o Photography 

o Games 

o Restaurants and Nightclubs 

o Videogames and multimedia 

• Articles for women and men 

o Shoes 

o Cosmetics and Perfume 

o Personal care 

o Jewellery, watches and optics 

o Fashion and accessories 

• Travel: 

o Flight offers 

o Hotel offers 

o Trips 

o Rent vehicles with and without engines. 

o Rural tourism 

o Luxury Travel

o Holidays and weekends 

o Business trips 

• Children’s products: 

o Products for Babies 

o Children’s shoes 

o Toys/ Educational games 

o Baby / Youths clothes 

• Music / Books 

• Training/ Employment 

• Health and Wellbeing: 

o Food 

o Ecology and Environment 

o Health, Healthy Life 

• Funeral services 

• Sports: 

o Team sports(Football, Basketball, etc.) 

o Maritime sports 

o Adventure and radical sports 

o Sports equipment 

o Fitness 

o Tennis, Golf, skiing and cycling

Mubawab has established a mechanism by which users can reject said services, simply and at zero cost.

To do so the user must enter his/her Personal menu, select Notifications and de-activate the relevant sending options in the Email section. Users can also de-activate this service by following the instructions at the bottom of the email.

#### 7- Cookies and IPs

The user accepts the use of cookies and IP follow-ups. Our website traffic analyzer uses cookies and IP follow-ups that allow us to collect data for statistical purposes, such as: date of first visit, number of visits, date of last visit, URL and domain from which it proceeds, explorer user and screen resolution. However, the user may decide to deactivate and/or eliminate these cookies by following the instructions given by their Internet browser.

Advertising on this site includes Google AdSense, a system that uses "cookies" to display publicity content that relates to what pages the user is viewing.

When a user accesses a site that utilizes Google AdSense, it introduces a cookie into his browser allowing Google to collect the information about the user's activity and publish Google AdSense advertising relevant to the user's browsing experience.

The user can deactivate Google cookies by deactivating cookies in their browser.

#### 8- Right of Data Opposition, Correction and Updating

The user is entitled to access this information and to rectify it if the data are erroneous and to give up the services of $url_country Notices should be sent to Mubawab, S.L, Calle Creueta 44, 08202 Sabadell (Barcelona), Spain or Contact Us.

The treatment of personal data and the sending of communications by electronic means are in line with the regulations established in EU data protection law and the Services of the Information Society and Electronic Trade law.

#### 9- Security measures

Mubawab has employed appropriate physical, procedural and technological measures to help protect your personal and/or other information from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we CANNOT guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your information for improper purposes. You may remove your information from the Site at anytime, but parties who have gained access may have retained a copy of your personal and/or other information in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of personal and/or other information saved to the Site.

#### 10- Modification of the privacy policy

Mubawab may update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended Privacy Policy on the Site and/or by sending a notice to the email address you provided. Your continued use of the Site shall constitute your consent to such changes and you will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy.

#### 11- Applicable legislation

The General Conditions of Use and the remaining legal conditions of the Website are governed in each and every one of their aspects by Spanish law.

If you have questions or suggestions, please Contact Us.

Effective Date: July 1, 2010
